# ABIGAIL DEGEYTER

# UX/UI Design Student



317-400-9396



abigailkdegeyter@gmail.com



507 | Tomahawk Trail Martinsville, Indiana

# Degree

Comprehensive Design is a degree that explores the links between many different areas of art and design. The curriculum mainly focuses on the concept of design thinking. This encourages students define design issues and create solutions to these issues through research and technology. With the incorporation of a minor in human-centered computing I will be on the best path for achieving success in a career of UX design.

#### **Skills**

### **Design Methods**

Affinity Diagrams

Personas

Prototyping Scenarios

Sketches

Storyboards

**Usability Tests** 

#### Tools

Adobe Suite

Rhino

HTML

JavaScript

CSS

Database

#### **EDUCATION**

2022 Bachelor of Science in Comprehensive Design, Minor in Human-Centered Computing; 3.25 Overall GPA

Indiana University / College of Art and Science

/ Luddy School of Informatics, Computing, and Engineering

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Freelance Graphic Designer

2020 - Present

Coherent Live LLC | Bloomington, IN

- •Use Adobe Illustrator to create a logo that will represent the company as a whole
- •Create and produce the design and layout of graphic material for online marketing and blog
- ·Assist in creative decisions regarding color, style and layouts

#### Stylist Associate

May 2019 - Aug 2019

Von Maur | Greenwood, IN

- ·Assist Customers in their entire shopping experience including; greeting, selecting merchandise, assisting in the fitting room, and completing purchases
- ·Creating transfers of merchandise, and phone orders
- Merchandising new merchandise stock

# **Customer Care Specialist**

May 2018 - Aug 2018

Lowes | Indianapolis, IN

- ·Handle daily customer calls, and phone orders
- ·Signing up customers for in store credit card
- ·Assisting in the purchases and returns of merchandise
- ·Assuring overall customer satisfaction

## **Projects**

#### **UX Design Simulation Project**

Oct 2019 - Nov 2019

Whirlpool, Internet of Things Problem

- · Created a solution to Whirlpools problem of connecting house hold devices by creating a smart fridge that connected a variety of Whirlpool's resources
- •Gathered data on users through research and interviews of varying demographics
- Created a story board, presentation, and prototype of the solution

### Solving Problems with Technology

Nov 2019 - Dec 2019

Potholes of Bloomington Problem

- · Tasked with the problem of finding a solution that would solve a rift between Bloomington's local government and the residents of Bloomington
- · Developed the idea of creating a app that would easily inform the local government of existing potholes in the area by encouraging residents to report them through a reward
- Developed a prototype of the app as well as a website to give further information on the research and background of the solution